{
    "id": "itochan",
    "name": "イトウヒロキ",
    "yomi": "Hiroki Ito",
    "text": [
        "こんにちはです☀︎イトウ ヒロキです。<br>1996年生まれの岡山県出身です。",
        "Hi ☀︎ I'm Ito Hiroki from Okayama born in 1996"
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Twitter",
            "href": "https://www.twitter.com/kirohitooo/"
        },
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/takapop_1996/"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "What taste of ramen noodle do you like?",
            "jp": "どの味のラーメンが好きです？",
            "yes": "tonkotsu (pork bone broth)",
            "left": "豚骨",
            "no": "salt",
            "right": "塩"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "What color do you like?",
            "jp": "好きな色は、何ですか？",
            "yes": "green",
            "left": "緑",
            "no": "red",
            "right": "赤"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "What taste of ice cream do you like?",
            "jp": "何味のアイスが好きですか？",
            "yes": "vanilla",
            "left": "バニラ",
            "no": "green tea",
            "right": "抹茶"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "What do you draw with?",
            "jp": "絵を描く時は、何を持ちますか？",
            "yes": "a pencil",
            "left": "鉛筆",
            "no": "a ballpoint pen",
            "right": "ボールペン"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "MUJI is about?",
            "jp": "無印良品といえば、何ですか？",
            "yes": "curry",
            "left": "カレー",
            "no": "cosmetics",
            "right": "化粧水"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Which do you like?",
            "jp": "どちらが好きですか？",
            "yes": "a pillow",
            "left": "枕",
            "no": "a cushion",
            "right": "クッション"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Where do you drink melon soda?",
            "jp": "メロンソーダは、どこで飲みますか？",
            "yes": "at a cafe",
            "left": "喫茶店",
            "no": "at Karaoke shop",
            "right": "カラオケ屋さん"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "What do you imagine when you hear <b>hachi</b>?",
            "jp": "『はち』といえば、どちらですか？",
            "yes": "8",
            "left": "8",
            "no": "a bee",
            "right": "蜂"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "What animal do you like?",
            "jp": "好きな動物は、何ですか？",
            "yes": "cat",
            "left": "猫",
            "no": "bear",
            "right": "熊"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Which way do you go?",
            "jp": "どちらに行きますか？",
            "yes": "toward left",
            "left": "左へ",
            "no": "toward right",
            "right": "右へ"
        }
    ]
}